

Maxim Sheshukov



Berlin, Germany



+4915256004078



sheshukovmaxim@gmail.com



go-maxus-go

A results-oriented software engineer with 8 years of work experience. Well-versed in producing efficient, reusable and readable code. Initiative and creative, constantly looking for ways for improvement. Some of my personal projects are Foody (Flutter), Marbles Puzzle (Qt, QML), di (C++).

Work experience

Software Engineer C++ 06/2019 - nowadays

Software Engineer C++/Qt 11/2018 - 03/2019 **Software Engineer C++**

01/2018 - 06/2018

Software Engineer C++/Qt 10/2017 - 12/2017

Software Engineer C++/Qt 03/2016 - 10/2017

Software Engineer C++ 11/2013 - 03/2016

BinarySpaces, Berlin, Germany

- Reduced project save time by 50% by implementing data cache in RAM.
- Implemented a release MVP feature Rotary Table for machine setup.

Escape Technology, Moscow, Russia

• Implemented moving avatars like in Telegram messenger.

Luxoft, Moscow, Russia

• Added a debugger for Lua scripts.

2GIS, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented the algorithm for choosing the fastest server.

Movavi, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented a Slideshow Maker that became a successful product.

SoftLab-NSK, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Designed a no bullets biathlon training system for children.

Education

Computer science / Physics master's degree 09/2006 - 06/2012

Novosibirsk State University, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Section of automation of physical and technical research. Department of physics.

Skills

Development Codina Languages C++, STL, Qt, QML Git, CI, CD Russian OOP, SOLID, TDD Dart, Flutter English **Boost** Algorithms, patterns German

Hobbies



Programming









Btw, I use Arch

Strengths

Critical thinking Teamwork Reliability **Initiative** Leadership **Quick learning**